(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Amane Kanata 1st Solo Live "LOCK ON" ARIAKE ARENA
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ
ATTENTION: To all visitors
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is ok.
Amane Kanata 1st Solo Live "LOCK ON" 2次販売グッズ
Amane Kanata 1st Solo Live "LOCK ON" 2nd Sales Goods
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ
ATTENTION To our visitors
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
2次販売グッズ
2nd round of merchandise sales
あ、こっちこっちこっち！
Ah, over here, over here!
今日二人じゃないんすね。
So it's not just the two of us today?
え？二人？
Huh? The two of us?
さっきの、ここで会った人たち。
Those people from before, I just met them here.
心で...
In my heart...
♪「ラヴ・パレード」ORANGE RANGE
♪ "Love Parade" by ORANGE RANGE
Joyしとこうぜ！
Let's Joy!
JOYSOUND X1
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is ok.
Amane Kanata 1st Solo Live “LOCK ON” 2次販売グッズ
Amane Kanata 1st Solo Live "LOCK ON" 2nd Round Merchandise Sales
ATTENTION
ご来場のお客様へ
To all attendees
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights
during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is ok.
Amane Kanata 1st Solo Live "LOCK ON"
2次販売グッズ
2nd Merchandise Sale
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
ATTENTION To all visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is okay.
Amane Kanata 1st Solo Live LOCK ON 2次販売グッズ
Amane Kanata 1st Solo Live LOCK ON 2nd Round Merchandise Sale
あ、あ、あ、あ
A, a, a, a
聞こえますか、皆さん？
Can you hear me, everyone?
イェーイ！本日は天音かなた 1st Solo Live『LOCK ON』にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you all for coming to Amane Kanata's 1st Solo Live "LOCK ON" today!
イェーイ！天音かなたです！イェーイ！
Yay! I'm Amane Kanata! Yay!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure everyone enjoys the live show until the end, I have a few announcements to make.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, recording, and the use of recording equipment during the performance are strictly prohibited.
そして、みんな！万が一具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、絶対に無理をせず、お近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
Also, everyone! In the unlikely event that you feel unwell, please don't push yourself and notify a nearby staff member.
絶対だよ、おーい！
Promise me, okay!
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
Moshing, diving, throwing objects onto the stage,
他の皆さんの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
or any other acts that cause trouble for others or obstruct the performance are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってください！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
えらい！
Good job!
本公演は映像配信、写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に配置され、客席が映り込む場合がございます。
For this performance, cameras for video streaming and photography are placed within the venue, and the audience seats may be captured on film.
イェーイ！いいよな！
Yay! Cool, right!
映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware that video and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
はーい！ありがとう！
Okay! Thank you!
またライブのハッシュタグは #打ち抜けかなた なので、
Also, the hashtag for the live show is #UchinukeKanata,
みんなハッシュタグを使って配信で見てくれているみんなも、
so everyone, including those watching the stream, please use the hashtag.
お前らは…帰り道かな？
As for you all... maybe on your way home?
帰り道にね、またハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください！
On your way home, please use the hashtag and keep the excitement going!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
それでは開演までもう少し、みんなで一緒に盛り上がっていきましょう！
Well then, just a little longer until the show starts, let's all get excited together!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Amane Kanata 1st Solo Live LOCK ON
負けない 絶頂 さきがけ撃ち最強
Unbeatable, at the peak, the strongest first strike
呪われて 愛されて 偽らぬ光を見せて Oh
Cursed and loved, show me a light that doesn't lie, oh
しっかりキャッチ
Catch it firmly
そこから逃げ切ってはしないで
Don't run away from there
止めないで高鳴り
Don't stop the throbbing
鏡にはツギハギ
Patches in the mirror
あいつが心揺らして
That guy shakes my heart
Attention!
Knock it out!
声出していかなきゃ
Gotta raise our voices
無敵な I I I I love it!
Invincible I I I I love it!
着飾れほら ピースブレイク 弾こう
Dress up, look, let's play the peace break
I I I I love it!
野生感燃やせ CRY
Burn the wild soul, CRY
行くぞ！有明アリーナ！！
Let's go! Ariake Arena!!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
靴の音 響いて
Sound of shoes echoing
待ち構えてた眩しさは 震え始める Vulnerable
The waiting radiance begins to tremble, Vulnerable
あいつは I I I I love it!
That guy is I I I I love it!
聞き飽きたよ 遠吠え 迷う
I'm tired of hearing it, howling, lost
夢見てても 起きてなきゃ意味がない
Even if you dream, it's meaningless unless you're awake
傷ついても 勝つだけ 花束まで 音響け
Even if hurt, just win, let the sound echo until the bouquet
踊らせて 強がり 欲張りで 華麗に Say
Let me dance, with bluff and greed, beautifully Say
ひたむき 嘘でも 泣けば 只々只々只々
Single-mindedly, even if it's a lie, if you cry, just just just just just
Ba-Ba-Ba-Bang!
おイラは君なんだ 笑顔でいれちゃう おまじない
I am you, a spell to keep you smiling
後悔なんてしてない日々だよ ご機嫌な Right now
Days I don't regret at all, feeling good Right now
無敵な I I I I love it!
Invincible I I I I love it!
着飾れほら ピースブレイク...
Dress up, look, Piece break...
I I I I love it!
野生感 壊せ CRY
Destroy the wild soul, CRY
クラップしてください！！
Please clap your hands!!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
一人待つ 汽車なのに賑わってた
Waiting alone for a train, yet it was crowded
不安 不安 不安ばっか また追い込んじゃったんだ
Just anxiety, anxiety, anxiety, I've cornered myself again
チカチカって真っ赤な弁当 結晶変えた誰か
Someone who changed the bright red lunch box crystal
ゆらゆら運んでた いなくなっちゃったさ
Transporting it swayingly, they've gone away
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
カンカラってカンカラ待つ 公衆網が歌ってた
The public network was singing from a can
ガランガランにしても また詰まっちゃったんだ
Even if I emptied it, it's clogged again
フラフラって真っ青な弁当 やつれてないさ
Swayingly, the pale blue lunch box, not worn out
あれあれ聞こえますか それ吐きなっちゃったんだ
Oh oh, can you hear me? That's been vomited out
欠陥品と嘲笑して ろくでなしと見下して
Laughing it off as a defect, looking down as a good-for-nothing
あの貶した壊滅 マジで もしかして
That disparaged destruction, seriously, maybe?
あらあらこう見てただけ 希望になれ 恒久的
Oh my, just looking like this, become hope, permanently
良い子になるまで 愛してくれる？
Will you love me until I become a good girl?
大丈夫 どんどん焼いて満たして ぐちゃぐちゃに声肥して
It's okay, burn and fill more and more, making the voice messy
骨の髄まで ちゃんと奥まで ちゃんと I I I love it
To the marrow of the bone, properly to the depths, properly I I I love it
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
なりたいやりたい こっち足りないままに錆びなっちゃって
Want to be, want to do, this way not enough, becoming rusty as it is
可愛いね 偉いね おめめに映った音共も全部嘘
Cute, right? Great, right? All the noises reflected in the eyes are lies too
媚弱して 媚弱して 言葉なさず なでなでしてあげるから
Fawning, fawning, without words, I'll pet you
こちらへ 愛が上手だね エ・エ・エ やってるね
Come here, you're good at love, eh eh eh you're doing it
気がついたね 息が欠けたね ひとりだけで今日も過ごせたね
You noticed, right? Your breath was spent, you spent today alone again
日々が上手ね 血が上手ね 泣いたほうがキュンと来ちゃっても
Days are good, blood is good, even if crying makes your heart throb
あくめが上手から放たれて
Released from being good at evil
全てを撒き散らした私は
I who scattered everything
ありえないほど愛おしくて愛おしくて堪らない
I love you so much I can't stand it
だけど多分一発じゃ伝わらないから 今度は君の脳解いくらでも
But probably one shot isn't enough, so I'll untie your brain as much as I want
しゃらんね 君のせいじゃないもんね
Sharan-ne, it's not your fault
しゃらんね しゃらんね ねんねしたいよね もいっちょ
Sharan-ne, sharan-ne, want to sleep, right? One more time
しゃらんね しゃらんね 泣いても泣いても来ないね
Sharan-ne, sharan-ne, even if you cry, they won't come
しゃらんね しゃらんね 誰も返事しないもんね
Sharan-ne, sharan-ne, no one answers
あらあら もうそんな 傷つけたりしないで
Oh my, don't hurt them anymore
こんなバグだらけの世界になっちゃってごめん
Sorry the world became so buggy
大丈夫 安泰 結局ね
It's okay, peace of mind, after all,
真っ白な世界に今を
in a pure white world, I'll show you
見せないから ずっと今日も一緒
nothing, so we'll be together today too.
A-La-La-La 噛み付いてたんだ 気持ちになる
A-La-La-La, I was biting into that feeling.
本能的な線になれるまで 愛してあげるね
Until I become an instinctive line, I'll love you.
大丈夫 どんどん欲張ってみかして 秘密に恋子焦がして
It's okay, show me more of your greed, longing for secrets.
泣いちゃうくらい 笑っちゃうくらい ちゃんと愛 愛 愛
Enough to cry, enough to laugh, proper love, love, love.
Love you!
自分、陰キャですから。
Because I'm a gloomy character.
あぁ 怖い 人間が怖い！
Ah, scary! People are scary!
許して 見ないで！
Forgive me! Don't look at me!
でもちょっとは見て
But look at me a little bit.
ボロボロ ボロボロ ボロボロ 哀しきインキャラだバイバイ
Tattered, tattered, tattered. It's a sad gloomy character, bye-bye.
Ah no! Why no? インだもな！
Ah no! Why no? Because I'm introverted!
今日も 今日も ネガティブコア
Today, today too, negative core.
Ah no! Why no? インだもな！
Ah no! Why no? Because I'm introverted!
世界で一番 反対で
The most 'opposite' in the world.
袖が当たれば漏れる泣き声
If our sleeves touch, a sob escapes.
及ぶねの彼方 憂鬱マヂ
Beyond my reach, seriously melancholy.
終わらない会議始まる
An endless meeting begins.
うるせー！
Shut up!
知らねー！
I don't know!
嫌ねー！
I hate it!
デトックス求めて東奔
Running east and west seeking a detox.
西走！
Running west!
炎上！
Flaming!
挙動不審でごめんなさい
Sorry for my suspicious behavior.
ただ嫌われたくないだけなもんで
It's just that I don't want to be hated.
震える両手足りぬ冷や汗 飛ばっ 飛ばっ 飛ばっ
Trembling hands, not enough cold sweat. Fly! Fly! Fly!
笑おう 笑おう 手抜き笑おう
Let's laugh, let's laugh, a lazy laugh.
あはは、いふふ、なるほどですね！
Ahaha, ifufu, I see!
全然全然お構いなく
Not at all, not at all, don't mind me.
反省 反省 また反省だ
Reflection, reflection, reflection again.
胸の中を ワンツー 強く打つのに
Even though my chest beats strongly, one, two.
明日は今日より人間になりたい
Tomorrow I want to be more human than today.
Ah no! Why no? インだもな！
Ah no! Why no? Because I'm introverted!
真っ暗お部屋で反省会
A reflection meeting in a pitch-black room.
Ah no! Why no? インだもな！
Ah no! Why no? Because I'm introverted!
たどたどおもてで後悔中
Regretting with halting words on the outside.
空気を読むこと数千年
Reading the air for thousands of years.
声の聞こえに耳を澄まし
Straining my ears to hear the voices.
群れず 呼ばれず 関わらず
Not flocking, not called, not involved.
そう 誰が呼んだか 陰の者
Yes, someone called me 'the gloomy one'.
陰キャと呼ばれるこの生物は 心の中が非常に...
This creature called a gloomy character has a mind that is extremely...
0.5秒の間に何十何百といった...
...tens or hundreds of things in the span of 0.5 seconds...
妄想と心配事を同時に展開し...
...developing delusions and worries simultaneously...
そして自分にショート、フリーズ、タイマーするのである！
...and then they short-circuit, freeze, and time out on themselves!
急な無茶振り やだやだやだやだ
Sudden unreasonable demands, no no no no.
雑談トークの特等席 やだやだやだやだ
A front-row seat for small talk, no no no no.
誰かが待ってるエレベーター
The elevator where someone is waiting.
そう 我らこそ 陰の者
Yes, we are the gloomy ones.
陰キャに愛を！
Give love to the gloomy characters!
哀しきインキャラだバイバイ
It's a sad gloomy character, bye-bye.
目を合わせずにごめんなさい
Sorry for not making eye contact.
その明るい瞳が眩しくて
Because those bright eyes are too dazzling.
間が持たなくてごめんなさい
Sorry for not being able to keep the conversation going.
この会話も全てが演説で
Even this conversation is all just a speech.
挙動不審でごめんなさい
Sorry for my suspicious behavior.
ただ嫌われたくないだけなもんで
It's just that I don't want to be hated.
張り付く笑顔足りぬ冷や汗 飛ばっ 飛ばっ 飛ばっ
A plastered smile, not enough cold sweat. Fly! Fly! Fly!
笑おう 笑おう 手抜き笑おう
Let's laugh, let's laugh, a lazy laugh.
あはは、いふふ、なるほどですね！
Ahaha, ifufu, I see!
怖いくらいからきまくり
Coming from a place of being scary.
反省 反省 また反省だ
Reflection, reflection, reflection again.
鏡ですらも目をそらした
I even averted my eyes from the mirror.
明日は今日より人間になりたい
Tomorrow I want to be more human than today.
愛を！ 愛を！
Love! Love!
インキャに愛を！
Give love to the gloomy characters!
今日も 今日も ネガティブコア
Today, today too, negative core.
Ah no! Why no? インだもな！
Ah no! Why no? Because I'm introverted!
どうしてこうなりたいの！
Why do I want to be like this!
Ah no! Why no? インだもな！
Ah no! Why no? Because I'm introverted!
真っ暗お部屋で反省会
A reflection meeting in a pitch-black room.
Ah no! Why no? インだもな！
Ah no! Why no? Because I'm introverted!
陰キャの歌とか あり得ない！
A song about a gloomy character? Unbelievable!
みんなー！
Everyone!
ちょっと水飲んで、水飲みますね、一回。
I'll drink a bit of water, I'll drink water once.
うわー！ちょっとあつい！
Whoa! It's a bit hot!
おーい！
Hey!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
はい！ということでですね。
Alright! And with that...
へい！こんかなたー！
Hey! Kon-Kanata!
最高！
Awesome!
はい、キャッチコピーは握力50キロぎゅーぎゅー握りつぶしちゃうぞー、
Yes, my catchphrase is "I'll squeeze you tight
with my 50kg grip!"
ホロライブ4期生かなたそこと天音かなたです！
Hololive 4th Gen's Kanataso,
Amane Kanata here!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
ということでみんな、天音かなたファーストソロライブ
Anyway, everyone, thank you so much for coming to
LOCK ONにお越しくださりありがとうございます！
Amane Kanata's 1st Solo Live, "LOCK ON"!
いや本当にね、あの初めてのソロライブですよ、
No, really, it's my first ever solo live,
ちょっと皆さん。
everyone.
僕も念願でしたが、ちょっと平民のみんなも
It's been a dream of mine, and I'm sure you Heimin
この日を楽しみにしてたんじゃないのー！
have been looking forward to this day too!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
いや本当にね、僕の今までの活動、
Truly, I want to take all the feelings
ちょっとここにね、気持ちとかも全部、
from my activities up until now,
みんなと一緒にぶつけていけたらいいなと思ってるので
and put them into this with everyone,
今日1日楽しんでください！
so please enjoy the day!
ありがとうございます。はい、みたいな感じでね。
Thank you very much. Yes, like that.
あの、みんなアルバムいっぱい聴いてくれて、
You all listened to the album a lot,
コールまじですごいじゃん！おまえら！
and your calls are seriously amazing! You guys!
すごい！覚えてきてくれたんだね、ギリギリやったのに。ありがとう。
Amazing! You memorized them,
even though it was last minute. Thank you.
ありがとね。めっちゃギリギリやったの。ありがと。
Thank you. It was really last minute. Thanks.
え、そして皆さん、ちょっとぜひ紹介したいものがありまして、
Oh, and everyone, there's something
I'd really like to introduce.
なんと！
To my surprise...!
今回ガールズバンドを引き連れてきましたー！
I brought a girls band with me this time!
すごい！
Amazing!
いやもうね僕、夢でしたね、ガールズバンドというものが。
It's always been a dream of mine
to have a girls band.
ありがとうございます。ありがとうございます。
Thank you. Thank you.
本当に可愛いし。
They're really cute.
イエーイ、可愛いんですよ皆さん。
Yay, they're so cute, everyone.
あの、腕章も。生徒会の腕章もね。
Also, the armbands. The student council armbands too.
もう忘れ去られた初期の設定ですね。
It's an early setting that's already been forgotten.
こちらも、つけてくれてるから。
They're wearing them too.
僕あの生徒会のね、あの初期なんだけど覚えてる？
I was in the student council
at the beginning, do you remember?
あ、覚えてるわ。
Ah, you remember.
初期だ。生徒会長じゃないからね、はい。
It was the early days.
I wasn't the student council president, though.
ありがとう。ありがとうね。
Thank you. Thank you.
という感じでですね、あの、憧れ夢だったソロライブと
So, like this, the solo live and
ガールズバンド、そしてみんなが。ありがとう。
girls band I've always dreamed of,
and all of you. Thank you.
配信でもね、配信のおまえらも見てるかな。ありがとう。
To those watching the stream too,
are you guys watching? Thank you.
これ推しカメラっていうのがありまして、
We have this "Oshi Camera,"
ちょっと配信上ではね、イエーイ。
so on the stream... Yay!
アピールしてるね。まあね、この現地にいるみんなも、
I'm showing off. Well, since everyone here
配信でも見てくれるだろうから、ちょっと可愛くアピっとくわね。
and on the stream is watching,
I'll show off my cuteness a bit.
可愛い！ありがとう！
Cute! Thank you!
すご！これ脳汁がドバドバ出ますね。
Wow! This gets the dopamine flowing.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
ライブの感想も、コメントもイエーイ、ウオー、
The live impressions and comments... Yay! Whoa!
見てるって言ってる、見てる見てる、見てるよ、ありがとう。
You're saying you're watching?
I see you, I see you, I'm watching. Thank you.
ということで、こういったね、ライブの感想なんですが、
So, for live impressions like these,
ハッシュタグ「#打ち抜天音」で、
use the hashtag #UchinukeKanata.
あの配信で見てるおまえらも。現地のみんなは
For those watching the stream too.
For those here at the venue,
帰り際とか帰ったらとか、なんですけど。
maybe when you're leaving or after you get home.
#打ち抜天音でたくさんポストしてください！
Please post a lot with #UchinukeKanata!
イエーイ、ありがとう。ありがとうございます。
Yay, thank you. Thank you very much.
そしてなんとですね、ちょっと悲しいお知らせがここで。
And now, I have a bit of sad news.
YouTube、TikTokで無料チラ見せを見てる方は、
For those watching the free sneak peek
on YouTube and TikTok,
ごめんここまでです。あー！
I'm sorry, but this is the end. Ah!
なんてったってー。えー、ということでね、すみません。
No way! Well, with that, I'm sorry.
ここからあの、有料になってしまいます。有料コンテンツですね。
From here on, it will be paid content.
あんなすごいことが起きるかもしれませんよ。えー！
Something amazing like that might happen. Eh!
やばい！
No way!
ということでまだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは
So, for everyone who wants to
概要欄から配信サイトへよろしくお願いします。
keep getting hyped together, please check
the streaming site in the description.
何が起こるかわからない。ありがとう。
You never know what might happen. Thank you.
そしてですね、ステージの変化みんな気づいた？気づきましたか？
And also, did everyone notice the change
on stage? Did you notice?
すごいでしょ。さっきまで羽が開いてたんですけど、
Isn't it great? The wings were open
until a moment ago,
ご覧の通り閉じました。
but as you can see, they've closed.
これま、やっぱセオリーで考えますと、
Well, following the usual theory,
みんなの声が足りないってやつじゃないのー！
it must mean your voices aren't loud enough!
もっともっと、もっともっと！おらー！わー！
More, more! More, more! Come on! Whoa!
きたー！やるじゃん！
There it is! Not bad!
やるじゃん、みんな。ありがとう。
Not bad, everyone. Thank you.
みんなのおかげで羽もね、開き...
Thanks to everyone, the wings have... open...
ましたよ。ありがとうございます。
...I've. Thank you very much.
みんなの...
Everyone's...
あ！
Ah!
ほら静かになれば、かなた可愛い！
See, if you're quiet, Kanata is cute!
かなたー！
Kanata!
可愛いぞー！
You're cute!
うおー！
Whoo!
きゃー！可愛い！
Kyaa! Cute!
可愛い、可愛い、可愛い。ありがとうございます。
Cute, cute, cute. Thank you very much.
ということでね、羽もまた、ありがとう。
And with that, thank you for the wings too.
開きました！
They opened!
みんなの声も出てきたので、
Since everyone's voices have come out,
次の曲、行ってみよー！
Let's move on to the next song!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended. Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました。
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peak part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching.